Guide to the Marilyn Horne Foundation Records, 1991-2011 CTC.2010.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, 1994-2009; III.
  - On Wings of Song, 1996-2007; 2.
    - On Wings of Song - Alex Richardson, May 7, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - On Wings of Song, 2006-2007 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - On Wings of Song - Edward Parks, October 5, 2008 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - The Song Continues, 1994-2009; 3.
    The Song Continues... Festival is the Marilyn Horne Foundation's annual festival that focuses on the art song. The annual festival included the gala concert, several masterclass by world-renown singers, vocal seminars, and other duo recitals by the Foundation's roster of artists. This subseries of photographs is arranged chronologically.
    - Annual recital, 1994-1996 (Box 127, Folder 1-4)
    - Master Class - Christa Ludwig, January 14, 1997 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Master Class - Marilyn Horne, January 14, 1997 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Annual recital, January 15, 1997 (Box 127, Folder 7-8)
    - Roundtable Seminar, January 15, 1997 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Master Class - James Levine, January 14, 1998 (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Master Class - Joan Sutherland, January 15, 1998 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Roundtable Seminar, January 15, 1998 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Annual recital, January 16, 1998 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Master Class - Thomas Hampson, January 13, 1999 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Master Class - Marilyn Horne, January 14, 1999 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Roundtable Seminar, January 14, 1999 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Annual recital, January 15, 1999 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Master Class - Martin Katz, January 14, 2000 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Master Class - Regine Crespin, January 14, 2000 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Roundtable Seminar, January 14, 2000 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Annual recital, January 16, 2000 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Master Class - Shirley Verrett, January 17, 2001 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Master Class - Marilyn Horne, January 18, 2001 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Annual recital, January 19, 2001 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Master Class - James Levine, January 19, 2001 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Master Class proofs, January 2002 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Master Class - Warren Jones, January 16, 2002 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Master Class - Marilyn Horne, January 17, 2002 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Annual recital, January 18, 2002 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Master Class - Phyllis Curtin, January 18, 2002 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Master Class - Grace Bumbry, January 15, 2003 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Master Class - Brian Zeger, January 16, 2003 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Annual recital, January 17, 2003 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Master Class - Marilyn Horne, January 17, 2003 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Annual recital - Proofs from all events, 2004 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Annual recital - Lobby and outside Carnegie Hall, February 1, 2004 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Annual recital - Public relations photos, February 1, 2004 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Annual recital - Public relations photos, January 28, 2005 (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Annual recital - Proofs from all events, January 2006 (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - Annual recital, January 27, 2006 (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - Annual recital, January 26, 2007 (Box 132, Folder 1-2)
    - Annual recital - Proofs from all events, January 2008 (Box 132, Folder 3-4)
    - Duo recitals - Proofs, January 2009 (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - Master Classes - Proofs, January 2009 (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Annual recital, January 18, 2009 (Box 132, Folder 7-8)
    - Annual recital - Gala dinner, January 18, 2009 (Box 132, Folder 9)
    - Roundtable, January 22, 2009 (Box 132, Folder 10)
    - Annual recital - Proofs from all events, 2010 (Box 132, Folder 11)
- Audio/Visual Materials, 1995-2010; IV.
  There were over 200 audio recordings that were included with the Marilyn Horne Foundation's records. These recordings were never made commercially available. Most of these recordings are on CDs, but a small amount are on audio cassettes. There are also nearly 150 video recordings on DVD, VHS, Mini DV, and Beta SP.
  These recordings are divided into three subseries. Each subseries is arranged in chronological order. Each performance contains a note with venue and artist information, the format of the recording, and the length.
  - National Residency Program and other recordings, 1996-2001; 1.
    This subseries contains recordings of recitals presented by the Horne Foundation's national residency program. Also included in this subseries are a small collection of videos that were sent out to schools and performing arts groups that were prospects to participate in the program. These recordings are arranged in chronological order. Each performance contains a note with venue and artist information, the format of the recording, and the length.
    - Recital, January 9, 1995 (Box 133, Folder 1)
      National Residency Program recital at the Connecticut Grand Opera.
      Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation.
      Olafur Bjarnason, tenor and Vignir Albertsson, piano.
      - Live recording, Cassette, 60 minutes
    - Recital, August 11, 1995 (Box 133, Folder 2)
      National Residency Program recital at the Cape & Islands Chamber Music Festival, MA.
      Pamela Pantos, mezzo soprano.
      - Live recording, Cassette, 30 minutes
    - Recital, October 1, 1996 (Box 133, Folder 3)
      National Residency Program recital at Middlebury College Center for the Arts, VT.
      Russell Braun, baritone and Carolyn Maule, piano.
      - Video recording, VHS, 35 minutes
    - Recital, October 8, 1996 (Box 133, Folder 4)
      National Residency Program recital at Martin Luther King Jr. Middle School, CA.
      Heidi Murphy, soprano.
      - Video recording, VHS, 38 minutes
    - Recital, October 9, 1996 (Box 133, Folder 5)
      National Residency Program recital at Berkeley High School, CA.
      - Video recording, VHS, 38 minutes
    - Recital, September 22, 1997 (Box 133, Folder 6)
      Margaret Lattimore, mezzo soprano.
      - Video recording, VHS, 49 minutes
    - Recital, February 25, 1999 (Box 133, Folder 7)
      National Residency Program recital at Monterey High School, CA.
      Artists unknown.
      - Video recording, VHS, 53 minutes
    - Recital, February 1999 (Box 133, Folder 8)
      National Residency Program recital at Middlebury Junior High School, VT.
      Mary Phillips, mezzo soprano.
      - Video recording, VHS, 32 minutes
    - Radio performance, February 1999 (Box 133, Folder 9)
      Vermont Public Radio program.
      Mary Phillips, mezzo soprano interview and performance. With Ted Taylor, piano.
      - Vermont Public Radio program, Cassette, 50 minutes
    - Recital, March 4, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 1)
      National Residency Program recital at Palm Valley School and Palm Springs High School, CA.
      Greg Turay, tenor.
      - Video recording, VHS, 90 minutes
      - Video recording - includes additional performance footage and student interviews, VHS, 100 minutes
    - Recital, May 10, 1999 (Box 134, Folder 2)
      National Residency Program recital at Duke Ellington School for the Arts, Washington D.C..
      Rodney Gilfry, baritone; Grant Gershon, piano.
      - Video recording, VHS, 81 minutes
    - Recital, February 9, 2000 (Box 134, Folder 3)
      National Residency Program recital at Aurora School, VT.
      Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation and Middlebury College.
      Sari Gruber, soprano; Cameron Stone, piano.
      - Video recording, VHS, 41 minutes
    - Recital, April 6, 2000 (Box 134, Folder 4)
      National Residency Program recital at Lincoln East High School, NE.
      Scott Hendricks, baritone.
      - Video recording, VHS, 22 minutes
    - Promotional video, February 27, 2001 (Box 134, Folder 5)
      Marilyn Horne Foundation video sent out to schools to promote the Foundation's education program.
      Footage taken from performance at Robert Louis Stevenson High School, CA by Lester Lynch, baritone.
      - Video recording, VHS, 18 minutes
    - Recital, April 6, 2001 (Box 135, Folder 1)
      National Residency Program recital at Elizabeth Hall at Stetson University, FL.
      Presented by Central Florida Cultural Endeavors, Inc. in association with the Stetson University School of Music, and the Marilyn Horne Foundation.
      Daniel Weeks, tenor; Donna Loewy, piano.
      - Live recording, 2 CDs, 73 minutes
    - Promotional video, May 2001 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      Footage taken from performance at Sea Side High School, CA by Daniel Weeks, tenor.
      - Video recording, VHS, 19 minutes
      - Video recording - includes additional performance footage, VHS, 23 minutes
    - Promotional video, June 7, 2001 (Box 135, Folder 3)
      Footage taken from multiple performances by various artists.
      - Video recording, VHS, 24 minutes
    - Promotional video, June 27, 2001 (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Video recording, VHS, 23 minutes
    - Promotional video, July 10, 2001 (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Video recording, VHS, 2 minutes
    - Promotional video, August 21, 2001 (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Video recording - includes Marilyn Horne voiceover and subtitles, VHS, 22 minutes
    - Recital, August 24, 2001 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      National Residency Program recital at Robert Louis Stevenson School, CA.
      Lester Lynch, baritone.
      - Video recording, VHS, 19 minutes
    - Radio performance, January 27, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 2)
      Saint Paul Sunday radio program, recorded at WITF Harrisburg, PA.
      Marilyn Horne interviewed by host Bill McGlaughlin; Dina Kuznetsova, soprano; Troy Cook, baritone; Brian Zeger, piano perform live in the studio in St. Paul, Minnesota.
      - Saint Paul Sunday radio program, Cassette, 70 minutes
    - Recital, March 10, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      Sundays Live recital at the Leo S. Bing Theater, CA.
      Presented by the City of Los Angeles Cultural Affairs Department in cooperation with the Los Angeles County Museum of Art, the Marilyn Horne Foundation, and Santa Monica College.
      Ramone Diggs, tenor; Nino Sanikidze, piano.
      - K-Mozart radio broadcast, CD, 67 minutes
    - Recital, August 3, 2002 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      The 2002 Marilyn Horne Foundation Awards in honor of Gwendolyn Koldofsky at Abravanel Hall, CA.
      Presented by the Music Academy of the West.
      Judges: Marilyn Horne, Michael Benchetrit, Fred Carama, Barbara Hocher, Gayletha Nichols.
      Jeffrey N. Behrens, tenor; Melissa Citro, soprano; Sasha Cook, mezzo soprano; Deborah Domanski, mezzo soprano; Thomas Glenn, tenor; Holli Harrison, mezzo soprano; Shauna Keene, soprano; Dimitrie Lazich, baritone; Susanna Phillips, soprano; Justin Plank, baritone; Silvia Vasquez, mezzo soprano.
      Phillip Kirchmann, piano; Margaret McDonald, piano; Nino Sanikidze, piano; Jerome Tan, piano; Christopher Zemliauskas, piano.
      - Live recording, 3 CDs, 190 minutes
    - Recital, May 16, 2003 (Box 136, Folder 5)
      National Residency Program recital at unknown school.
      Jennifer Aylmer, soprano; Jonathan Kelly, piano.
      - Video recording, DVD, 40 minutes (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Video recording, Mini DV, 40 minutes
    - Recital, June 16, 2003 (Box 135, Folder 6)
      NYC Education Program recital at unknown school.
      Jennifer Aylmer, soprano.
      - Video recording, VHS, 40 minutes
    - Recital, July 26, 2003 (Box 135, Folder 7)
      The 2003 Marilyn Horne Foundation Awards in honor of Gwendolyn Koldofsky at Abravanel Hall, CA.
      Judges: Marilyn Horne, Michael Benchetrit, Mary Lou Falcone, Barbara Hocher, Robert White.
      Antonio Abate, tenor; Melinda Blum, soprano; Timothy Fallon, tenor; Wendy Bryn Harmer, mezzo soprano; Joni Henson, soprano; Elisa Kaufman, soprano; Megan Latham, mezzo soprano; Shannon Mercer, soprano; Steven D. Pence, bass; Howard Reddy, baritone; Rodell Aure Rosel, tenor; Faith Sherman, mezzo soprano; Erica Strauss, soprano; Alexander Tall, baritone; Charles Temkey, bass; Anna Jane Uzzell, mezzo soprano; Ami Vice, soprano; Erik Nelson Werner, baritone.
      Phillip Kirchmann, piano; Miloš Repický, piano; Marie-Ève Scarfone, piano; Dexter Shepherd, piano; Jerome Tan, piano; Carol Wong, piano.
      - Live recording, 4 CDs, 224 minutes
    - Tenth anniversary compilation project, 2003 (Box 135, Folder 8)
      These draft compilations were done in honor of the foundation's tenth anniversary in 2004. The finished product is was released as The Marilyn Horne Foundation 1994-2004 10th anniversary celebration album: highlights of the Foundation's first decade of recitals.
      - First draft, June 5, 2003; 3 CDs, 208 minutes
      - First draft, 3 CDs, 204 minutes
      - Draft, September 15, 2003; 3 CDs, 142 minutes
    - Recital, July 24, 2004 (Box 135, Folder 9)
      The 2004 Marilyn Horne Foundation Awards in honor of Gwendolyn Koldofsky at Abravanel Hall, CA.
      Judges: Marilyn Horne, Michael Benchetrit, Sheri Greenawald, Barbara Hocher, and Bill Vendice.
      Antonio Abate, tenor; Elaine Alvarez, soprano; Thorsteinn Arbjornsson, tenor; Laura Compton, Shelby L. Condray, bass; mezzo soprano; Brocha Tamara Evans, soprano; Timothy Fallon, tenor; Joni Henson, soprano; Kathleen Kim, soprano; Dimitrie Lazich, baritone; Deniela Lehner, mezzo soprano; Whitaker Mills, bass baritone; Steven David Pence, bass; Mari-Yan Pringle, soprano; Viktor Rud, baritone; Brian Edward Thorsett, tenor; Anna Jane Uzzell, mezzo soprano; Alavaro Vallejo, tenor; Nimrod Weisbrod, baritone; Janette Zilioli, soprano.
      Megan Gale, piano; Rob Gurvits, piano; Lara Hanoian, piano; Wei-En Hsu, piano; Marie-Ève Scarfone, piano; Jerome Tan, piano.
      - Live recording, 4 CDs, 214 minutes
    - Recital, April 29, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 10)
      National Residency Program recital at the Martha-Ellen Tye Recital Hall, IA.
      Presented by Ames Town & Gown Chamber Music Association in cooperation with the Marilyn Horne Foundation.
      Deborah Domanski, mezzo soprano; Phillip Kirchmann, piano.
      - Live recording, 2 CDs, 101 minutes
    - Recital, July 23, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 11)
      The 2005 Marilyn Horne Foundation Awards in honor of Gwendolyn Koldofsky at Abravanel Hall, CA.
      Judges: Marilyn Horne, Michael Benchetrit, Mary Lou Falcone, Barbara Hocher, Brian Zeger.
      - Live recording, 4 CDs, 225 minutes
    - Recital, September 17, 2005 (Box 135, Folder 12)
      National Residency Program recital at the Bromeley Family Theater, PA.
      Presented by the University of Pittsburgh at Bradford Spectrum Series in association with the Marilyn Horne Foundation.
      Nicole Cabell, soprano; Spencer Myer, piano.
      - Live recording, CD, 70 minutes
    - Recital, July 22, 2006 (Box 135, Folder 13)
      The 2006 Marilyn Horne Foundation Awards in honor of Gwendolyn Koldofsky at Abravanel Hall, CA.
      Judges: Marilyn Horne, Mary Lou Falcone, Barbara Hocher, Speight Jenkins, and Robert White.
      Antonio Abate, tenor; Gutemberg Amaral, bass-baritone; Nicholas Bentivoglio, tenor; Holly Boaz, soprano; Todd Boyce, baritone; Eugene Chan, baritone; Amanda Crider, mezzo soprano; Julie Davis-Ramsey, soprano; Nicole Farbes-Lyons, soprano; Rena Harms, soprano; Evan Hughes, bass-baritone; Michelle B. Johnson, Daveda Karanas, mezzo soprano; Jonathan Kimple, bass; soprano; Sidney Outlaw, baritone; Edward A. Parks III, baritone; Alek Shrader, tenor; Nathan Stark, bass-baritone; Alvaro Vallejo, tenor; Ami Vice, soprano; Audrey Walstrom, mezzo soprano
      Ming Hay Kwong, piano; Keun-A Lee, piano; Christopher Mokrzewski, piano; Kyung-Eun Na, piano; Tamara Sanikidze, piano; Christopher Thompson, piano.
      - Live recording, 3 CDs, 237 minutes
    - Recital, November 17, 2006 (Box 135, Folder 14)
      National Residency Program recital at Baird Recital Hall, NY.
      Presented by the UB Department of Music in association with the Marilyn Horne Foundation.
      William Ferguson, tenor; Jerome Tan, piano.
      - Live recording, 2 CDs, 87 minutes
    - Work Sample, February 18, 2007 (Box 135, Folder 15)
      Recital work sample #2.
      Sidney Outlaw, baritone.
      - Video recording, VHS, 45 minutes
    - Recital, February 23, 2007 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      National Residency Program recital at Bromeley Family Theater, PA.
      Katherine Rohrer, mezzo soprano; John Parr, piano.
      - Live recording, CD, 75 minutes
    - Recital, July 21, 2007 (Box 137, Folder 2)
      The 2007 Marilyn Horne Foundation Awards in honor of Gwendolyn Koldofsky at Abravanel Hall, CA.
      Judges: Marilyn Horne, Michael Benchetrit, Thomas Hampson, Barbara Hocher, Ken Noda (absent), and Gianna Rolandi.
      Leticia Brewer, soprano; Ernest Alvarez, tenor; Eugene Chan, baritone; Jason Eck, bass-baritone; Christopher Herbert, baritone; Katherine Lerner, mezzo soprano; Brandon McReynolds, tenor; Amber Opheim, soprano; Sidney Outlaw, baritone; Damien Pass, bass; Stephen Ray, baritone; Nadine Sierra, soprano; Nathan Stark, bass; Jessica Stavros, soprano; Joshua Stewart, tenor; Alexander Tall, baritone; Andrea Trusty, mezzo soprano; Ami Vice, soprano; Audrey Walstrom, mezzo soprano; Stephanie Washington, soprano (did not perform due to illness); Allison Watson, soprano; Bray Wilkins, tenor.
      Joel Ayau, piano; Chuck Dillard, piano; Anna Fateeva, piano; Karen Kyung-Eun Na, piano; Eric McEnaney, piano; Tamara Sanikidze, piano.
      - Live recording, 4 CDs, 240 minutes
    - Recital, October 26, 2007 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      Elaine Alvarez, soprano; Christopher Cano, piano.
      - Live recording, CD, 60 minutes
    - National Residency program promotional video, 2007 (Box 137, Folder 4)
      Marilyn Horne Foundation dvd sent out to schools to promote the Foundation's education program and introduce students to the vocal recital and classical song.
      Performing in the video are Jennifer Aylmer, soprano and Jonathan Kelly, paino.
      - What is a Classical Song? - Video recordings, September 10, 2007; 5 Mini DV tapes, 75 minutes
      - What is a Classical Song? - DVD master, November 21, 2007; DVD, 15 minutes
      - What is a Classical Song? - Master, November 28, 2007; Mini DV, 15 minutes
      - What is a Classical Song? - DVD revised master, November 28, 2007; DVD, 15 minutes
      - What is a Classical Song? - Master, December 11, 2007; Mini DV, 15 minutes
      - What is a Classical Song? - DVD with packaging, DVD, 17 minutes
      - What is a Classical Song? - Graphics DVD
      - What is a Classical Song? - Audio files, 2 CDs, 69 minutes
    - Recital, April 9, 2008 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      Dame Myra Hess Memorial Concert at GAR Hall: Chicago Cultural Center, IL.
      Presented by the International Music Foundation and Chicago Dept. of Cultural Affairs.
      Meredith Arwady, contralto; Mikael Eliasen, piano.
      - WFMT Memorial radio broadcast, CD, 45 minutes
      - Video recording, DVD, 44 minutes
    - Recital, April 15, 2008 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      Jason Hardy, bass; Jerome Tan, piano.
      - Live recording, CD, 65 minutes
    - Recital, July 26, 2008 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      The 2008 Marilyn Horne Foundation Awards in honor of Gwendolyn Koldofsky at Abravanel Hall, CA.
      Judges: Marilyn Horne, Michael Benchetrit, Barbara Hocher, Kenneth Merrill, and Joan Morris.
      Zachary Altman, baritone; Julie Davis, soprano; Krista de Silva, mezzo soprano; Jennifer Feinstein, mezzo soprano; Abdiel González, baritone; Adam Hall, tenor; Christopher Herbert, baritone; Adam Lau, bass-baritone; Anna Mihanović, mezzo soprano; Djoré Nance, bass; Simone Osborne, soprano; Andrew Owens, tenor; Edward Parks, baritone; Kevin Ray, baritone; DeAndre Simmons, bass-baritone; Jessica Stavros, soprano; Joshua Stewart, tenor; Joanna Taber, soprano; Ashley Renée Watkins, soprano; Bray Wilkins, tenor; Célia Zambon Wollenberg, soprano; Olivia Wong, soprano; Janette Zilioli, soprano.
      Joel Ayau, piano; Anna Fateeva, piano; Brent Funderburk, piano; Suzy Smith, piano; In-Sun Suh, piano; Lucas Wong, piano.
      Not participating in the contest: Brenda Rae, soprano; Alek Shrader, tenor; In-Sun Suh, piano.
      - Live recording, 4 CDs, 281 minutes
    - Recital, September 27, 2008 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      Hanan Alattar, soprano; Richard Masters, piano.
      - Live recording, 2 CDs, 83 minutes
    - Recital, February 6, 2009 (Box 138, Folder 5)
      National Residency Program recital at St. Louis Art Museum, MO.
      Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation and the Saint Louis Art Museum.
      Wendy Bryn Harmer, soprano; Christopher Cano, piano.
      - Live recording, 2 CDs, 95 minutes
      - Live recording, DVD data disc, 95 minutes
      - WXQR radio broadcast, February 28, 2009; CD, 54 minutes
    - Recital, February 7, 2009 (Box 138, Folder 6)
      National Residency Program recital at United Church of Santa Fe, NM.
      Presented by Santa Fe Concert Association and the Marilyn Horne Foundation.
      Susanna Phillips, soprano; Myra Huang, piano.
      - Live recording, CD, 66 minutes
      - WXQR radio broadcast, May 30, 2009; CD, 55 minutes
    - Recital, February 13, 2009 (Box 138, Folder 7)
      National Residency Program recital at Hahn Hall, Music Academy of the West, CA.
      Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation and the Music Academy of the West.
      Evan Hughes, bass baritone; Jerome Tan, piano.
      - Live recording, 2 CDs, 85 minutes
      - WQXR radio broadcast, April 18, 2009; CD, 60 minutes
    - Master class, March 19, 2009 (Box 138, Folder 8)
      Marilyn Horne Master Class at Roberts Recital Hall, AL.
      Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation and University of Alabama in Huntsville.
      Marilyn Horne
      - Video recording, DVD, 160 minutes
    - Recital, March 20, 2009 (Box 138, Folder 9)
      Marilyn Horne Foundation / Huntsville Chamber Music Guild 10th Anniversary Recital recital at Trinity United Methodist Church, AL.
      Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation, the Huntsville Chamber Music Guild, and University of Alabama in Huntsville.
      - Video recording, DVD, 116 minutes
    - Recital, July 25, 2009 (Box 138, Folder 10)
      The 2009 Marilyn Horne Foundation Awards in honor of Gwendolyn Koldofsky at Abravanel Hall, CA.
      Judges: Marilyn Horne, Mary Lou Falcone, Margo Garrett, Barbara Hocher, and Peter Kazaras.
      Derrell Acon, bass baritone; Zachary Altman, baritone; Gutemberg Amaral, bass baritone; Tyrone Chambers, II, tenor; Benjamin Clements, bass baritone; Julia Cramer, soprano; Julia Dawson, mezzo soprano; Betsy Diaz, soprano; Jennifer Feinstein, mezzo soprano; Jeffrey Hill, tenor; Kathryn Louise Lewek, soprano; Darla Mattern, soprano; Ronnita Miller, mezzo soprano; Richard Ollarsaba, bass baritone; José Rubio, baritone; DeAndre Simmons, bass; Marco Stefani, tenor; Joshua Stewart, tenor; Andrea Trusty, mezzo soprano; Ashley Renée Watkins, soprano; Rodney Westbrook, tenor; Célia Zambon Wollenberg, soprano.
      Adam Bloniarz, piano; Melanie Cancade, piano; Daniel Fung, piano; Lio Kuokman, piano; Rebecca Mordo, piano; Sahar Nouri, piano.
      Not participating in the contest, one of last year's winners: Simone Osborne, soprano.
      - Live recording, 4 CDs, 241 minutes
    - Cruise concerts, September-October 2009 (Box 138, Folder 11)
      Concerts performed on the Corinthian II during the Marilyn Horne Celebration in the Mediterranean cruise from September 29 - October 9, 2009.
      Presented by the Marilyn Horne Foundation and the Santa Fe Concert Association.
      Nicole Cabell, soprano; Sasha Cook, mezzo soprano; Kelly Markgraf, baritone; Joshua Stewart, tenor; Tamara Sanikidze, piano; Jerome Tan, piano.
      - Live recoding, 2 CDs, 95 minutes
    - Recital, October 6, 2009 (Box 138, Folder 12)
      Joshua Hopkins, baritone; Jerad Mosbey, piano.
      - Live recording, CD, 64 minutes